Are you Mr. Li?
Thanks.
Enjoy your meal.
I'll take this, then.
Okay.
The task force cast a tight dragnet,
closing in step by step.
Du Qingbo resorted to covert tactics,
creating hurdles at every turn
to obstruct the task force.
As the battle between good and evil peaked,
no one could have anticipated
that a single expert
would turn the tide completely.
Professor?
Professor.
I left the engineering materials report on your desk.
Xiao Wang,
you should take this money back.
I looked it up online.
A bribe of 300,000 is considered a huge amount.
In severe cases,
it can mean up to three years in prison.
So,
you'd better take it back.
Brother Zhang,
he wants to return the money.
What's the matter, Professor Gong?
Not enough money?
No...
Or do you want something else?
This money...
I really can't take it.
Don't worry.
I won't say a word to anyone.
Am I being too nice to you?
I call you "Professor" out of respect,
and you actually think you're somebody?
Take the respect when it's given.
Otherwise, don't even think about surviving in Jianzhou.
Take the money
and get the hell out.
Be good.
Do as you're told.
Everything all right at the company?
An expert was uncooperative and wanted to return the money.
Who?
Named Gong.
Gong Jianlin.
But after my
care and guidance,
he came around.
Don't worry, it's taken care of.
All right.
Got it.
You can go now.
Hello?
Hello.
Is this Comrade Gong Jianlin?
Speaking.
I'm with the Municipal Discipline and Inspection Committee.
We need to ask you about a few things.
Please come tomorrow at 2:00 PM
to Conference Room 3 at the Discipline and Inspection Committee.
All right, sure.
Who is it?
What are you up to, Professor Gong?
I've been knocking forever.
Over that little bit of money,
you're not planning to report me, are you?
What are you talking about? Are you joking?
Of course not.
C-Come in, have a seat.
Professor Gong.
Mr. Du.
Aren't you going to invite me in?
Come in.
Please.
Professor Gong,
I heard
you don't want to work with us anymore.
That can't be true, can it?
It's a misunderstanding.
Not at all.
Here, please.
Have some water, Mr. Du.
That's what I thought.
You know,
a while back,
I came across a video.
There was someone in it
who looked exactly like you.
Take a look and see if it's you.
Here, show it to the professor.
Come on.
Let's watch it together.
Here.
"Stop it, Professor Gong."
You...
Look.
It really is you.
Take a look.
Professor Gong,
a man of your standing...
there are certain things you just shouldn't do.
Wait, no...
If your family and employer found out,
it would look terrible.
You set me up!
Why are you setting me up? Why?!
So what if we did?
Don't terrify Professor Gong.
Professor Gong,
you need to have faith in Jinxin.
Look at Jinxin Company.
Have we ever had any trouble all these years?
Never.
Why?
Because we run a legitimate business.
Plus, I have plenty of friends.
I even have friends in the Discipline and Inspection Committee.
The...
The Discipline and Inspection Committee?
The Discipline and Inspection Committee.
Did they contact you?
No, Mr. Du...
They did contact me,
but I swear I didn't say anything!
Believe me.
I really didn't say anything!
You...
Mr. Du!
I didn't say anything!
Not a single word!
Tell you what, Professor Gong.
Why don't you
go unwind with Zhang Lei for a few days?
Get some rest.
Let's go.
Professor Gong.
Wait, Mr. Du...
Let's go have some more fun.
I really didn't say anything, Mr. Du!
I really didn't, Mr. Du!
Let's go.
Qingbo!
What's wrong?
Did you have a nightmare again?
Get ready to leave the country early.
I've already sorted out the paperwork.
Take Yanyan with you.
A person has to know when to stop.
What about you?
I know what I'm doing.
The Discipline and Inspection Committee contacted me.
They—
They said they want to talk to me.
I think they must have
gotten hold of some evidence.
If I come clean about everything now,
would it count as turning myself in?
Director He,
how you feel right now,
I completely understand.
Everyone is trying to smooth things over right now.
Besides,
our connections higher up
have pretty much been taken care of.
If you lose your nerve right now,
you'll only end up causing trouble.
But the Discipline and Inspection Committee is no joke!
Director He,
over the years,
how much has passed through your hands,
you should know best.
You can't just get on and off this ship as you please.
If Young Master Qin finds out,
he won't be very happy.
All right, Mr. Du.
Director He is a smart man.
He knows how to weigh his options.
Right?
D-Don't worry.
I... I'll stick with everyone
through thick and thin.